<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>talk on Keisha S Perkins</title>
    <link>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/categories/talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in talk on Keisha S Perkins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/categories/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Programming with Automation Apps</title>
      <link>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/automation-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/automation-apps/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re in the age of STEM right now and everyone is screaming that &amp;ldquo;Everyone should learn to code&amp;rdquo; when what they really mean is that more people should learn how to program. Programming is a skill that will help most of us, as most of us deal with computers on a daily basis. Programmatic Thinking is a skill that will help almost anyone, because programmitic thinking is just problem solving in a systematic way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up and Running With HUGO</title>
      <link>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/upandrunningwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:08:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/upandrunningwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>I spoke at Baton Rouge Hack Night about my favorite static site generator, HUGO.
 Hugo is a great static site generator that&#39;s super fast and lightweight. This talk demos the steps for getting a site up and running, adding a few posts, and choosing a theme. I really recommend digging into the HUGO docs as well as the HUGO Community Forum for more in-depth explanations of how to use HUGO for your own site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How One .PSD File Transformed My Workflow</title>
      <link>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/how-one-file-transformed-my-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 02:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keishasperkins.github.io/kayesspeadesign_2/blog/how-one-file-transformed-my-workflow/</guid>
      <description>I create a good deal of media for my church, and sometimes that media needs to be used in many ways. Perhaps the event flier that I create for a pre-service loop of slides needs to also be made to fit social media, or be printed and handed out.
Up until recently I solved this issue by first designing something for the church&amp;rsquo;s presentation screen at a 16:9 ratio, then resizing and tweaking the design to meet whatever other needs where given to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>